linuxine.com 2015-03-20

# Terms and Conditions

**Terms &Conditions of use of Linuxine.com**

  1. **Personal Use.** The Service is made available to you for your personal use only. Due to the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (which is available at http://www.ftc.gov/ogc/coppa1.htm), you must be at least thirteen (13) years of age to use this Service. You must provide current, accurate identification, contact, and other information that may be required as part of the registration process and/or continued use of the Service. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your Service password and account, and are responsible for all activities that occur thereunder. Linuxine reserves the right to refuse service to anyone at any time without notice for any reason.
  2. **Proper Use.** You agree that you are responsible for your own communications and for any consequences thereof. Your use of the Service is subject to your acceptance of and compliance with the Agreement. You agree that you will use the Service in compliance with all applicable local, state, national, and international laws, rules and regulations, including any laws regarding the transmission of technical data exported from your country of residence. You shall not, shall not agree to, and shall not authorize or encourage any third party to: (i) use the Service to upload, transmit or otherwise distribute any content that is unlawful, defamatory, harassing, abusive, fraudulent, obscene, contains viruses, or is otherwise objectionable as reasonably determined by Linuxine; (ii) upload, transmit or otherwise distribute content that infringes upon another party's intellectual property rights or other proprietary, contractual or fiduciary rights or obligations; (iii) prevent others from using the Service; (iv) use the Service for any fraudulent or inappropriate purpose; or (v) act in any way that violates the Program Policies, as may be revised from time to time. Violation of any of the foregoing may result in immediate termination of this Agreement, and may subject you to state and federal penalties and other legal consequences. Linuxine reserves the right, but shall have no obligation, to investigate your use of the Service in order to determine whether a violation of the Agreement has occurred or to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request.
  3. **Your Intellectual Property Rights.** Linuxine does not claim any ownership in any of the content, including any text, data, information, images, photographs, music, sound, video, or other material, that you upload, transmit or store in your Linuxine account. We will not use any of your content for any purpose except to provide you with the Service.
  4. **Representations and Warranties.** You represent and warrant that (a) all of the information provided by you to Linuxine to participate in the Services is correct and current; and (b) you have all necessary right, power and authority to enter into this Agreement and to perform the acts required of you hereunder.
  5. **Registration obligations.** You shall provide Linuxine with accurate registration information. Failure to do so will constitute a breach of the Terms of Use, which may result in termination of your Linuxine account. You may not (i) select or use as a Linuxine id a name of another person with the intent to impersonate that person; (ii) use as an Linuxine id a name subject to any rights of a person other than you without appropriate authorization. Linuxine reserves the right to refuse registration of, or cancel a Linuxine id in its discretion.
  6. **Links The Services may provide, or third parties may provide, links to other World Wide Web sites or resources.** Because Linuxine has no control over such sites and resources, you acknowledge and agree that Linuxine is not responsible for the availability of such external sites or resources, and does not endorse and is not responsible or liable for any content, advertising, products or other materials on or available from such sites or resources. You further acknowledge and agree that Linuxine shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on any such Content, goods or services available on or through any such site or resource.
  7. **Privacy.** As a condition to using the Service, you agree to the terms of the Linuxine Privacy Policy as it may be updated from time to time. Linuxine understands that privacy is important to you. You do, however, agree that Linuxine may monitor, edit or disclose your personal information, including the content of your emails, if required to do so in order to comply with any valid legal process or governmental request (such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order), or as otherwise provided in these Terms of Use and the Linuxine Privacy Policy. Personal information collected by Linuxine may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which parent company The Open Company Partners LLC or its agents maintain facilities. By using Linuxine, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.
  8. **Indemnification.** You agree to hold harmless and indemnify Linuxine, and its subsidiaries, affiliates, officers, agents, and employees from and against any third party claim arising from or in any way related to your use of the Service, including any liability or expense arising from all claims, losses, damages (actual and consequential), suits, judgments, litigation costs and attorneys' fees, of every kind and nature. In such a case, Linuxine will provide you with written notice of such claim, suit or action.

**Linuxine.COM PRIVACY POLICY  
**

Linuxine has created this privacy policy to demonstrate our commitment to the privacy of the members and clients. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy, and how we treat personal information collected from our affiliates.

**What this Privacy Policy Covers**  
This privacy policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information collected by us through a website owned and operated by us.

This privacy policy does not apply to the practices of companies that are not in our direct subjection, or of persons not employed by us, including any third-party content contributors bound by contract and any third-party websites to which our websites may link.

**Collection and Use of Personal Information**  
You may visit our websites without revealing any personal information. However, we need certain personal information if you wish to purchase our products, register a member account, receive our newsletter, or use certain our services.

If and where required, this information may include your contact information and/or your company contact information. We will use this information to reply to your inquiries, to provide you with requested products and services, to set up your memberвЂ™s account, and to contact you regarding new products and services.

By accessing our services and voluntarily providing us with the requested personal information, you consent to the collection and use of information in accordance with this privacy policy.

**Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information**  
We automatically receive and record certain types of non-personal information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page you requested. We may use this information to customize the advertising and content you see and to fulfill your requests for certain products and services. However, we do not connect this non-personal data to any personal information collected from you.

We also allow third party companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. These cookies are not connected to any personal information. Third party cookie usage is subject to their own privacy policies, and we assume no responsibility or liability for their use.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**  
We may disclose your personal information to third parties who work on our behalf to provide products and services requested by you. We may share personal information for these purposes only with third parties whose privacy policies are consistent with ours or who agree to abide by our policies with respect to personal information.

We may otherwise disclose your personal information when: (a) We have your express consent to share the information for a specified purpose; (b) We need to respond to subpoenas, court orders or such other legal process; (c) We need to protect the personal safety of the users of our websites or defend the rights or property of ours; (d) We find that your actions on our websites violate our Terms of Use document or any of our usage guidelines pertaining to corresponding products or services.

**Consent**  
If you do not consent to the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information as outlined in this policy, please do not provide any personal information to us. If you have provided personal information to us and cease to consent to its use or disclosure as outlined herein, please notify us at admin [at]Linuxine.com.

**Security**  
Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be considered 100% secure. However, your information stored with us is protected for your privacy and security. In certain areas of our websites, as identified on the site, we use industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.

We also safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access, through access control procedures, network firewalls and physical security measures.

Further, we retain your personal information only as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes identified above or as required by the governing law.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
We may at any time, without notice to you and in its sole discretion, amend this policy from time to time. Please review this policy periodically. Your continued use of our websites after any such amendments signifies your acceptance thereof.

**Questions or Suggestions**  
If you have questions or suggestions about this privacy policy, or your own personal information, please e-mail us at support[at]Linuxine.com

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
